Dear Governor Ivey.
My name is Michael Everette.
I'm a retired lieutenant from the Alabama
Department of Corrections, Holman Prison.
My name is Keith Watson.
I worked for Alabama Department of
Corrections for 21 years.
My name is Ernest Stanton, retired
correctional officer.
For around 20 years or so.
I worked on Death Row most of my time.
My name is Freddie Howard.
I'm a retired correctional officer.
I'm a community person now, I teach Sunday
School, I'm a person that cares about God.
My name is William James, I'm conservative, I
support law enforcement, and I support
law and order.
Mark is a man who deserves to be saved.
I think Mark Jenkins is a good person and
I do not think Mark should be executed.
Mark brings an atmosphere of peace to a
very,
very violent world.
I consider him as a model inmate, and I
believe if he was given a second chance,
he'll be a model person.
When things are going crazy and haywire, Mark will
be a voice of reason in any turbulent
situation.
I was the first officer to hire Mark as a
hall runner.
We had to have a lot of trust in hall runners
because they had more time out of their
cells than the other inmates.
Mark earned my trust.
I do not take executions lightly.
And I am asking Governor Ivey to grant clemency
for inmate Mark Jenkins on death row.
So I can only say, I hope that he gets the
best come out for him.
Governor, I voted for you and have
supported your tenure.
You've said you care about the voices of
correctional officers and that you have our
back.
I'm asking you to look at these letters.
The officers that I work with at Holman, the
officers who have signed these letters of
support, they know Mark.
They know and I know Mark deserves to have
his sentence commuted.
God gives us a chance every day.
You got up this morning.
I got up this morning.
He could have took us last night.
He could have took us on our way here.
But he gave you another chance.
That says to you, there's more work for you
to do.
That God is awesome and is in control.
And he's a God of love.
And love covers a multitude of sins.